Amir Ghorbani UX/UI Product Designer

Scan here for portfolio



(UK) 07414885307 Phone

Website https://amir-ghorbani.github.io/portfolio/

amir.qhorbani.desiqn@qmail.com Gmail

Instagram @savor_amir @ux.ui.aq

Linkedin www.linkedin.com/in/amir-ghorbani-**Behance**

https://www.behance.net/amirghorbanil

Skills

Xd Id 7 Adobe XD, InDesign and Figma

HTML, CSS, JavaScript, A-Frame

✓ Data Visualisation

Ai Ps Illustrator and Photoshop

3d modelling in Fusion 360 and C4D

Ae Adobe After Effects

Drawing and Digital painting

Having spent the last five years working my way up in various roles within visual arts, I am now on a path that leads me to utilise my creativity and resourcefulness. Studying UX/UI has been a chance to challenge me and to improve my creative personality. I enjoy the design process as much as the final product and I would like to develop my career in the User Experience and User Interface field. I am innovative, technical, organised, approachable, energetic and ambitious. I enjoy working with creative people and finding the best ways in which to deliver our visions to audiences and make our world a better place.

Experience

UX/UI designer - Assurium - (Oct 2020 - present)

Assurium is an independent information technology service company. At Assurium, I am the UX/UI designer. Leading initial concept discovery, Ideation, wireframing, prototyping (Adobe XD), usability testing and execution of final design (Wordpress, Elementor, HTML, CSS, JS).

Technical Assistant Prototyping - Ravensbourne University London - (Sep 2021 - present)

I am working as part of the prototyping team to keep ensure production schedules are met. An ability to utilize 3d modelling software for the purpose of designing builds to be sent to 3D printers, laser engravers, etc. Ability to work collaboratively with community members, students, faculty and staff in an inviting and encouraging manner.

Freelance Information Design and Data visualisation - (Mar 2021 - present)

Information design includes diagrammatic, pictographic, and typographic visualisation techniques of information. The skills to develop narratives and identify new trends through data analysis and visualisation to add value to projects and support clients in reporting progress on the implementation of their sustainability commitments.

Workshop Organiser and Front of House Member - House of Illustration, London - (2017 - 2019)

Assist in the running and invigilation of gallery spaces; Undertake Front of House duties in the shop, and assist on events and artist talks.

Freelance artist, London and Berlin - (2015 - Present)

- Graffiti and Murals Anna Landsberger Internationales Jugendzentrum, Berlin. StillSTAND project - A project of Urban Spree and Senor Schnu, Berlin.
- Tutoring drawing sessions and creating graphic novels.

Education

Ravensbourne University London — BA (Hons) UX/UI Design - (2020 - Present)

Open College of Arts — BA(Hons) Graphic Design - (2018 - 2019)

University of Karaj (Iran) — Civil Engineering (BS) - (2003 - 2008)